Or, uh, Ticket to Ride?
Hearthstone?
I... what would you be
the happiest losing at?
(Penny:)I don't want to
play a game, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Wow, and I remember when you
loved playing games with me.
(Sheldon:)Maybe Penny isn't the only
relationship you're phoning in.
It's not that I'd
stopped trying,
it's just how
relationships progress.
(Leonard:)They start with infatuation,
(Leonard:)but over time mellow into
something more comfortable.
(Sheldon:)Hmm. Yeah, you're right.
(Sheldon:)It's like when
I first encountered
(Sheldon:)the Pythagorean Theorem.
(Leonard:)You know,
I was blown away
(Sheldon:)that the square
of the hypotenuse
(Sheldon:)was the sum of the squares
of the opposite sides.
Yeah, but now
I'm just like "eh."
(Howard:)Okay, this grid
represents the room.
(Howard:)All we need to do is plot out
where each squeak is
(Howard:)and we can find a quiet
path to the crib.